jenny-bird.com 2017-06-21

# Terms of Use | Jenny Bird

Welcome to the Jenny Bird website, www.jenny-bird.com (the “Site”), owned and operated by Jenny Bird Holdings Inc. and its affiliates (“Jenny Bird”). 

  Jenny Bird provides you with access to and use of the Site subject to your compliance with the Terms. No material from the Site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted or distributed in any way, except as specifically permitted on the Site. The Site, including all of its information and contents, such as text, data, images and graphics  (“the Site Content”) is Jenny Bird property and is protected by patent, trademark and/or copyright under Canadian, United States and/or foreign laws. Except as otherwise provided on the site, you may not use, download, upload, copy, print, display, perform, reproduce, publish, modify, delete, add to, license, post, transmit, or distribute any of the Site Content from the Site in whole or in part, for any public or commercial purpose without the specific prior written permission of Jenny Bird.

PROPERTY RIGHTS

As between you and Jenny Bird, Jenny Bird is the owner and/or authorized user of any registered or unregistered trademark or trade name appearing on the Site, and is the copyright owner or licensee of the Site Content on the Site, unless otherwise indicated. The Jenny Bird logos, designs, titles, phrases and product names and the copyrights, trademarks, service marks, trade dress and/or other intellectual property in such materials (collectively, “Jenny Bird Intellectual Property”) are owned by Jenny Bird and may be registered in Canada, the United States and internationally. You agree not to display or use the Jenny Bird Intellectual Property in any manner without Jenny Bird’s prior permission.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND JENNY BIRD

Q.  What type of information does Jenny Bird collect and use?

A.  You may be asked to provide certain personal information to us for the purpose of using the jenny-bird.com website (the “Website”), subscribing to receiving electronic communications from Jenny Bird, processing a sale or providing you with other Jenny Bird related services. Examples of information that could be personal information include your name, address, gender, date of birth, language preference, email address, telephone number, credit card information, personal opinions, social media usernames or other social media identification.

Q.  How does Jenny Bird use my personal information?

A.  Jenny Bird collects personal information to, among other things, (1) respond to your feedback, comments, or questions, (2) notify you about our products, services and other Jenny Bird related events and news, (3) monitor Website and social media traffic for market research purposes, (4) comply with legal and regulatory requirements, (5) statistical research, (6) processing a sale, and (7) credit card, PayPal, or email money transfer verification and processing. 

Q.  How does Jenny Bird protect my personal information?

A.  Jenny Bird takes appropriate steps to keep your personal information secure and confidential. This includes implementing effective physical, administrative, and technology safeguards, and retaining your personal information only as long as is necessary, or as required by law. 

Q.  When is my personal information disclosed to third parties?

A.  At Jenny Bird, we know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will care for your information sensibly. We do not distribute your information to third parties or business affiliates without your prior consent. If your personal information is sent to a third party, Jenny Bird will take appropriate steps to ensure that such recipients safeguard your personal information and use the information only for authorized purposes.

Q. How does Jenny Bird obtain my consent to collect, use or disclose my personal information?

A. Consent may be express or implied, and depends on the way in which you interact with our Website, social media networking accounts, and at various in-person events (i.e. tradeshows, conferences, or cocktail parties). For example, in the check-out process on our Website, you will see an option to stay informed via email communication from us regarding new products, promotions and other Jenny Bird-related news. You provide your express consent to receive these email communications by checking the box provided.   
Alternatively, submitting personal information to Jenny Bird or its service providers and agents means that you have agreed by implication to Jenny Bird collecting, using and disclosing your personal information in accordance with Jenny Bird’s Privacy Policy. For example, you may have provided us with your business card during an in-person event and requested that we add you to our mailing-list. 

Q. How do I revoke my consent? 

A.  You may refuse to provide personal information to Jenny Bird or withdraw your consent at any time after you have provided personal information by contacting Jenny Bird. However, refusing or withdrawing your consent may prevent Jenny Bird from completing your transaction, enabling certain features of our Website, or providing you with information about new products, promotions and other Jenny Bird-related news. 

Q.  How do I unsubscribe from Jenny Bird’s email newsletters? 

A.  Jenny Bird is committed to ensuring compliance with privacy and anti-spam legislations in all jurisdictions it operates in and will only send you newsletters with your continuing consent. You may unsubscribe at any time using a link provided in each email message or simply by contacting us and expressing this desire. If you unsubscribe by using the link provided in the email, you will be unsubscribed from all future email newsletters immediately. If you use other methods of communicating this request, your request will be honoured within ten (10) days of Jenny Bird receiving the request, if not sooner. 

Q. Who do I contact if I have a question, concern or complaint in connection with the Privacy Policy?

A. Please contact **:**   
Adam Kohn  
508-174 Spadina Ave.  
Toronto, ON  M5T2C2  
Phone: [1-844-520-BIRD](tel:1-844-520-2473) (US/International) / [647-346-2473](tel:1-647-346-2473) (Canada)  
Fax: 647-342-0528  
Email: [customerservice@jenny-bird.com](mailto:customerservice@jennybird.com)

For more information, please see Jenny Bird's full Privacy Policy, viewable [here](http://jenny-bird.myshopify.com/pages/privacy-policy).
